My Lady.
Where are you going?
I must go and do my duty.
Isn't your duty right here?
Last night, you were much bolder than this.
You should not speak like that.
Why not?
I am only speaking the truth.
Do I need to remind you how bold you were last night?
Or have you already forgotten?
I remember.
Then that is enough.
I was afraid you would pretend to forget.
Because I... could never forget what happened last night.
You are teasing me.
You're just realizing that?
I've been doing this from the very beginning.
Kaew!
You're here quite early this morning.
Yes,
I came early today.
Didn't you just come out of the Lady's room?
Kaew,
I have something to warn you about.
Last night, I went down by the waterfront
and I saw something.
You shouldn't get that close to the young mistress again.
Because of the difference in your social status, things can never work out between you two.
Stop this before the Lord finds out.
I'm warning you out of goodwill.
I understand.
The weather is lovely today, don't you think?
Why are you stepping back?
I am just being careful.
Careful of what?
Stay with me at the house tonight, Kaew.
That is not appropriate.
What did you come across?
Is something wrong?
Tell me, Kaew.
My feelings are inappropriate.
We are too different.
You... are the child of Luang Wisanu,
while I am just a servant.
And besides,
you know that I am a woman.
A love like this is impossible.
Love makes everything possible.
Only you are being a coward.
How would you feel if I disappeared?
What are you going to do?
If you don't want anything to happen to me,
Speak your true feelings.
See? You feel the same way I do.
You just don't dare to admit it.
Don't come to tend to me this evening.
I want to be alone.
Deal with him.